birdsbit.com 2017-12-29

# BirdsBit.com - free bitcoin faucet!

Birds-Bit.com.com Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.   

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address, Bitcoin Address or other details to help you with your experience. 

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you While Playing the game or enter information on our site. 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

      **•** To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services. 

**How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. 

We do not use an SSL certificate 

      **•** We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information 

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

**We use cookies to:**

      **•** Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.   

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. 

However, you can still place orders . 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**     
www.Birds-Bit.com.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**     
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.Birds-Bit.com.com.    
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.Birds-Bit.com.com and other sites on the Internet.     
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....    
Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.Birds-Bit.com.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  

www.Birds-Bit.com.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.birdsbit's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.  

**Log Files**   
Like many other Web sites, www.Birds-Bit.com.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website. 

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

** We have implemented the following: **

      **•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting 

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

Opting out:   
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf   

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously 

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. 

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above. 

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes: 

      **•** On our Privacy Policy Page 

Users are able to change their personal information: 

      **•** By emailing us 

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. 

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking 

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. 

We do not specifically market to children under 13. 

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. 

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email 

      **•** Within 1 business day 

We will notify the users via in site notification 

      **•** Within 1 business day 

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.Birds-Bit.com.com   
  
* * *

Bitcoin, as any other real or digital currency, must have a place where it is kept. Since crypto-currency is a comparatively new thing, people sometimes feel uncertain about working with it. In reality, everything is easy and fast. Here is a short guide on how to create and use a wallet for your crypto-currency.

Creating a Bitcoin Wallet is a matter of few minutes: you just put in your e-mail address and password (try blockchain.info, for example). Every wallet has an identifier, which you send to anyone who is going to make a transaction on your wallet. That’s all about Bitcoin Wallet creation.

However, there are some nuances about its usage and protection. You have to think about your Bitcoin wallet safety by paying attention to the following points:

\- choose thoughtfully the services providing Bitcoin wallets. It’s better to choose big and trusted platforms.

\- remember that Bitcoin rate is quite changeable. So it is a good idea to keep small sums on your Bitcoin wallet and convert excess funds into the currency of your country. Don’t put all your eggs in one basket.

\- make the copy of your wallet. It will help you to restore the wallet in case something happens to your PC or mobile. And encode the network reserve copies!

\- don’t forget to update your Bitcoin software: it will guarantee the better safety for your money.

One more thing that you should remember: Bitcoin transactions are not anonymous. Bitcoin is the most transparent payment system in the world – all transactions are public and are saved in Bitcoin network. Every Bitcoin wallet has its own address, which is shown when the transaction is conducted, so all transactions from this address are connected. If you care about confidentiality, then use one address only once and don’t publish your wallet address on your website or network page. 

* * *

The next few months the tempo of Ether cost has been steadily increasing. However, the last week bounce of the rate has advanced Ether to the highest league of crypto-currencies. That day (March, 3) the Ethereum capitalization increased about 26%, reaching $730 millions. It’s an impressive number, taking into account the fact that the number is bigger that the general capitalization of all other crypto-currencies, except Bitcoin. In addition, this is the tenth part of Bitcoin capitalization – no other currency has ever come so close to this number. It gives reasons to win the garland in blockchain technologies in future.

It is possible that such bounce rate was caused by the news that R3 consortium successfully led the parallel testing of five different blockchain technologies – Chain, Eris Industries, Ethereum, IBM, and Intel, drawing to process 40 banks. The innovations were highly evaluated by banks after introducing smart-contracts that should have simplified the secondary trading and purchase of securities (short-terms bonds with fixed income that are issued by corporations for additional funding). Every distributed ledger was substituted by similar smart-contract, which allowed banks to compare the difference between them. 

Vitalik Buterin, the Ethereum project founder, stated that in spite of Ethereum technology being a public blockchain, he appreciates corporate developments, based on the similar principles. It is great that there is a possibility to participate in such competitions, he added. The intellectual potential of smart-contracts, taking part in the competition, allows creating the new rules on the blockchain basis that will make possible any actions from simple distribution of assets to complex financial instruments.

Tim Grant, senior manager of R3 consortium is satisfied as well by the fact that they were able to unite eleven world financial institutions with the help of the distributed ledger on Ethereum basis. It showed how this new technology can be used for the solving of problems of real financial market processes, using smart-contracts for various actions with assets. In addition, it will give a great impulse to the development of the consortium itself and for the technology providers, he summed up.

* * *

Many world network users consciously limit the demonstration of various advertising information by using the special programs known as “ad blockers”. We won’t review the different kinds of such programs and browsers where they work, since this article is not about it. In return, let’s discuss whether it is ethical to use such software.

Advertising has always existed, but it wasn’t such evident at first. At the first place these were oral recommendations to buy some goods, rumors and jungle telegraph, actual topics on various meetings, etc. But such way of goods advertising or information about services is ineffective and limited. With the development of informational society the art of advertising has passed to the whole new level.

Today, the advertising in the press, TV or marketplaces in the city is surrounding us everywhere. We go to work – and read the ads on the street, we rest at home – and watch the ad on TV while waiting for the news or favorite movie. However, we don’t close our eyes to miss this information flow. Mainly we sip the information and grin and bear. Still, the trademarks, that are buying the TV advertisement time, won’t go bankrupt if you close your eyes or ears during the ads demonstration. While with the Internet ads the situation can be diametrically opposite.

The big amount of websites exists just for the fees received for placing ads on their pages. It means that every user visiting the website brings a minimal profit to it. But only in the case when the user sees the ad! If the site’s visitor uses ad blockers, the website receives nothing from your visit. And this is meanly the only revenue. So how ethically right will be using the software limiting ads showing? The author assumes that this would be incorrect to use the ad blockers against people that are doing something useful. Let’s be honest – if you receive some useful information, then why not tolerate the ad on the resource you are visiting?

* * *

Bitcoin is a digital currency created by a math genius Satoshi Nakamoto, the personality of whom still remains a mystery. Taking into account an accurately calculated and adjusted algorithm of crypto-currency functioning, one may assume that under his guidance the whole team of talented programmers was working, or even this is the collective pseudonym.

Created as an alternative to traditional fiat currencies, Bitcoin is a unique payment instrument, which is used with various goals: to pay for different transactions within the network, with the aim of accumulating or investment. 

When the first crypto-currency, overcoming the sceptics hesitations, started to develop and its rate began to grow, websites appeared that offered to get free Bitcoins after several simple actions and entering captcha (or without it) – these were the so called Bitcoin faucets. However, since payments are very small to be immediately withdrawn to the Bitcoin wallet, so for their withdrawal specific services for micropayments are used. Now, Faucetbox is used with this aim most frequently – it substituted Microwallet that started to fail in 2014.

Faucetbox is a system of crypto-currency micropayments. On this server small sums are transacted from the websites that give free Bitcoins, and from this server payments are calculated to the users’ Bitcoin wallets. The minimal sum for transaction is 1300 Satoshi (structural unit of Bitcoin), which is fulfilled automatically. However, this indicator can be set manually.

So you may ask a logical question – why you need this service if you can make payments independently. Momentary withdrawals of Bitcoin to Faucetbox allow miners to work more effectively, saving their time. To earn more or less sufficient sum, one Bitcoin faucet is not enough, you have to surf through several dozens and do it regularly. And now imagine how much time will take the manual withdrawal, if you sum up all transactions. In addition, the system of micropayments averts servers overloads and increases the speed of transactions.

One should pay attention to one more positive moment – all withdrawals that are fulfilled with the help of Faucetbox, are fee free, because they are provided within one resource. The majority of Bitcoin faucets works under the template of momentary withdrawal of Bitcoin into Faucetbox. The received money is transferred to the user’s account and are paid on the main wallet when the sum collected on it becomes equal to 1300 Satoshi (the sum can be changed in the settings).
